# Natalie Lima

Pasadena, CA 91107 natalielima97\_uiv@indeedemail.com +1 310 382 4510

Hi. I'm Natalie

I am a Los Angeles based UX/UI designer.

I always knew that some form of art would manifest into my life, who knew that I can actually design and be a part of our forever evolving technology. The artistry that stems from within came from dancing and singing which is has led me to venture off and understand what other forms of art do I enjoy. Curiosity has definitely lead me to want to be a UX/UI designer and maybe if I wasn't curious enough I wouldn't have taken the risk to take this path that I'm on now. I've worked in customer service for most of my life and obtained a lot of knowledge like interpersonal skills, empathizing with the customer, and consistently building my clientele. I then went on to becoming a nail technician and creating nail art, which was a very beautiful gift to my artistry. I wanted more for myself and I understand that the world of tech was always something that intrigued me. My mind is constantly racing and needing to explore my imagination, I feel that it's super vital to my existence and this is why I feel that being a designer can help bring forth my world for others to see. I am determined to build my knowledge and perfect my craft as a designer. My overall goal is to be a part of the evolution of technology and seeing how technology has paved the way towards a positive future.

# Work Experience

#### **Nail Technician**

Akashic Nails - Los Angeles, CA August 2016 to August 2020

- Provide manicure services to the customers and perform activities like assessing client needs, discussing requirements, shaping and smoothing nails, removing and applying nail polish, shaping artificial nails, and collecting payments.
- Empathizing with the customers to understand their needs by properly choosing the correct nail grooming technique.
- Accomplished nail art design by using different methods.
- Carefully making sure the customer does not feel discomfort during their experience with a nail technician.

#### Sales Associate

G Star Raw - Beverly Hills, CA November 2014 to December 2018

- Assuring that customers are acknowledged and they have help when needed
- Keeping track of inventory

### Education

# Certificate in UX/UI Design

Thinkful - Los Angeles, CA August 2020 to Present

Los Angeles city college 2011 to 2013

## Skills

- So ftware/Tools requirements, shaping and smoothing nails, removing and applying nail polish, shaping artificial nails, and collecting User research Figma payments. Competitive analysis Sketch
- Empathizing with the customers to understand their needs User stories InVision by properly choosing the correct nail grooming technique. User personas Adobe Illustrator
- Accomplished nail art design by using different methods. User testing Adobe Photoshop
- Carefully making sure customer does not feel discomfort UX design UsabilityHub during their experience with a nail technician. UI design GitHub Visual design G-Star RAW, Beverlyhills, CA 2014
- 2018 B H o bb ies randin g S ales Prototyping
- · Assuring that customers are acknowledged and they have Mock-ups
- help when needed
- Keeping track of inventor y Cycling Photography Travel Gaming
- Adobe XD
- figma

#### Languages

- Thai Expert
- · Laos Expert

#### Links

https://www.akashiccosmetics.com/

https://www.linkedin.com/in/natalielima7/

### Certifications and Licenses

## **UX/UI Designer**

August 2020 to January 2021